Digging Kitty
Brought to you by: Orange-Flash | ko-fi.com/OrangeFlash
Oh, it's you, Nobita.
Why are you crying?
This isn't like you, Suneo.
I'm but only a human being, so I cry when I'm sad.
What's with the kitty?
I wanted to adopt it, so I took it home...
but my mother refused to let me in and...
...told me to drop the kitty outside.
Hey, Doraemon, do you have any good idea?
Hmm,... let's see.
Why don't we ask her once again?
If we ask together, I'm sure she'll allow it.
This is why buying is bad.
Buying cat only to abandon it.
But if there are people who abandon cats...
...there must also exist, people like Suneo who'd take 'em home.
No can do. Cats only eat and do no work at all.
But this cat can catch mouse.
How rude! we don't have a mouse in our mansion.
Young master Suneo, abandon it and return.
We have no option.
Doraemon, do you have any good idea?
Let's see, a good idea, huh?
Something....
Nobita, you also try thinking.
if I'd get an idea after thinking, I'd not ask you, to begin with.
Ah, it's Shizuka-chan.
what are you all doing together?
That's it! If Shizuka brought the kitty to her home.
Will you please take it to your home?
I'd love to...
...but I already have a dog, canary bird and a hamster.
Hey guys! Shall I take it home?
I'd appreciate it, but...
But in return, one condition.
All of you will pull lottery.
Then, 1st prize ¥2000!
Oh, come on!
Then mind your own business.
I don't know what to do. I'm sorry for being unable to help.
We must find something productive.
How to make your mum happy, Suneo-kun?
Let's see... Precious gems are her favorite, so...
That's it! I have to turn this kitty into a "Digging Kitty".
"Treasure finding belt for Cats!"
By wearing this belt, you'll become a treasure hunting kitty...
like The Blossom Man's treasure hunting dog...
Do you have a ¥10 coin on you?
Since I bought this book, my pocket is empty.
I have it. Here.
Now let's test it out.
Let's go check it out!
I've buried the ¥10 coin somewhere around here.
This kitty should be able to find it.
Are you telling me to dig here?
Here it is!
Like this, if you find diamond or gold, your mum will be delighted.
She'd say it's alright to bring a cat.
Let's see what it finds.
It entered our mansion.
Did you find something here?
Someone stingy could have buried something here.
Anyway, let's dig and see...
"Mole Hand-gloves!"
You hit something?
Doraemon, what did you find?
I found this.
Mum, look what I have found!
It's the gem box that I had buried secretly.
Young master Suneo, did you find it?
What a unpleasant cat!
I've to find a better hiding place.
We made it worse.
For this cat, it's all-over!
Suneo, don't cry. You'll bring tears to my eyes as well.
Now this kitty must get adopted to Nobita's house only.
What? My house?
Nobita, it's all yours.
I'll bring cat-food once in a while, so take a good care of it.
What should I do?
No can do.
We have Doraemon, that's enough!
Doraemon ain't a pet though!
It'd be problem to feed one more belly in the family.
And you'll have enough of it by 3 days.
Stop being absurd and listen to me!
I'll listen to you.
Right, Doraemon?
Doraemon... what happened?
We're not done yet.
I have a family in the future, so I'll return to 22nd century.
Keep that kitty in my place.
Be reasonable!
I need you at this hour.
But if I weren't here....
First, let's covince mum.
Huh? Where's the kitty?
It ran to garden. Send it out after finding it.
Lost kitty! Where are you?
Ah! There it is!
The cliff has collapsed.
I dug a hole to hide gems when this slope collapsed and...
Thanks for rescuing me.
Young master kitty, please stay at our house forever.
Happy ending at last!
Isn't that great?
Yup, sure...!